I found myself lost and alone on this journey
Though my heart wandered far and wide, I could move not an inch
But now I can depart for any distant land
Now that we've met on this road
Even the unfamiliar songs of travelers
Can spark nostalgia in me when I'm with you
If the world we dreamed of exists somewhere,
Then let's go search for it beyond the wind
Through chilling dawns,
Through arid noons,
Through shivering nights,
Let's go see what lies at the end
Wolf and a New Journey
I thought our next meeting would be a tearful reunion. What a miserable sight.
They set us up.
This was the only thing I could protect.
God, you're a fine fool.
Face swollen from being beaten,
covered in dirt, wrists burned by rope...
And as you endure such humiliation,
the whole time you're protecting my neatly folded cloak from the rain like your life depends on it?
You're softhearted beyond belief!
You know...
I might be about to kill someone.
Holo...
I thought it was best to follow the plan and resume our journey as soon as possible,
so I opted not to fight those pups and took a more civilized approach.
Don't tell me that they made you...
Don't say it!
Forget about it.
It was my own decision.
But this is what I get in return?
To accept what's happened to you is entirely beyond me!
I'm going to find Lemerio and give him what he deserves.
W-Wait a second.
We have to take care of Liebert as soon as possible.
I hope you have a good reason for this.
They're going to kill Norah.
That girl is with her partner.
She'll probably be all right in any case.
Partner? Sheep dogs can only do so much!
You could...
I could what?
You could fight a hundred armed men without breaking a sweat.
I'll be in my wolf form, you know!
And that little girl is a shepherd!
Even so... could you do it?
An innocent person is about to die, and I can't just look the other way.
I'll reward you handsomely.
How?
I'll do my best to grant any wish as long as you don't ask for Norah's life.
Please.
No one can stop this but you!
Holo!
I should take my clothes off, right?
It'd be a shame to waste the time someone put into them.
Are you going to do it?
There's one condition.
I can't guarantee the life of anyone who annoys me.
Is that a deal?
Do as you will if that happens.
But I have faith in you.
You certainly have found yourself a way with words.
What a troublesome companion I've acquired.
Now, isn't there something you want to say?
Yes, it's a magnificent tail.
It was a little forced, but it'll do for now.
Now close your eyes for a moment.
Here, hop on.
You can hold on to my fur.
I'm going to carry you in my mouth if you fall off.
I'll hold on for dear life—
Hey.
What?
I really detest shepherds, you know.
I'm relieved to hear that.
Norah's going to quit working as a shepherd regardless of whether this plan succeeds.
I've decided on what I want.
What is it?
The finest peach preserves that money can buy!
Well, just don't bankru—
Lawrence-san and Holo-san?
When we found them, it was already too late.
We found them lying on top of each other.
Norah-san!
Sorry. I'm all right.
No, I understand how terrible this must be for you.
We have to pull ourselves together and fight to the end as those who survived.
Are you ready for this?
What?
They're right over there.
We've caught up to them already?
Indeed.
I can't see a thing.
Those bastards are well-armed.
There are around twenty of them.
That many?
It doesn't matter. Leave it all to me.
I'm going to lay low after I leap over them.
Jump off when I do.
You mustn't get close.
Protect the shepherd and the sheep!
Norah!
She was safe after all.
Take the shepherd and run!
Now!
Shepherd!
Protect me!
Enek...
This isn't good.
Holo's serious.
I'll give you three hundred Lumione if you protect me.
No...
Enek!
Wait!
Norah-san!
Um...
Yes?
You're not a ghost, are you?
Let me reveal the trick.
That wolf is Holo.
Holo... san?
You didn't kill him?
I was going to swallow him whole, but the gold he was carrying would have upset my stomach.
I see.
This is it.
Fiends! Do you think you're going to get away with this?
Good day, Liebert-san.
I wasn't the one who betrayed you.
Believe me... I didn't... I didn't...
This wolf has been summoned as a messenger of the one and only God.
Lies will do you no good here.
The cut you asked for was too much!
If we went along, we'd only be able to pay off our debts without making a profit.
That's why Lemerio asked me to do something about it.
You understand, don't you?
We're both merchants, after all...
Don't bring me down to your level!
Sorry about the trouble.
Oh, that's... okay...
Long story short, Lemerio Trading betrayed us.
They were planning to kill you, too.
I had a feeling something wasn't right, but...
Let's run away with the gold.
Let's see.
We have six hundred Lumione worth of gold even without having to resort to smuggling.
If we ignore those traitors at Lemerio Trading and split the gold amongst ourselves,
we'll have enough to live in luxury.
On the other hand, we wouldn't have been able to buy the gold without their contribution.
If we run away with the gold, they'll go bankrupt and end up on the streets with certainty.
That's why...
Holo!
We still have to live our lives after this.
There won't be an end to this grudge if we take revenge for their betrayal.
In that case...
And don't say you'll kill every last one of them!
I don't want the bread I buy tomorrow to have been paid for in blood.
There are many ways to end this.
Don't you want to make a decision that'll lead to a brighter future?
Holo, if it weren't for you, I'd be freezing to death by the forest right now.
I owe you my gratitude for listening to my selfish request.
But...
Enough. Do whatever you want.
Ah, my travel companion is tiresome beyond words!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Not at all.
I suggest we do the following.
So...
What?
Might I hear the truth now?
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb with me.
There's a limit to how generous a person can be.
You can decide whether you want to carry this gold into Lubinheigen.
You could also settle for your fair share of this gold right here.
I see.
But if we can manage to smuggle it safely, its value will
increase to six thousand Lumione through my connections.
S-Six thousand?
We could save Lemerio Trading with that kind of money.
I guess I can't hide anything from you.
There wasn't enough gold.
Six hundred Lumione was more than an exaggeration.
It's a hundred at best.
If you split the gold up, there wouldn't have been anything left after you paid your debt back.
You would have had to carry out the smuggling to make a profit.
Lemerio was in a desperate situation.
They only managed to get one-sixth of the amount we had agreed upon.
Once they got it inside, they probably could have gotten a thousand Lumione at most...
...so they knew they wouldn't have enough to pay for our silence from the very beginning.
It's probably why they agreed to our offer in the first place.
All right. I understand the circumstances, but...
Is anything else bothering you?
You didn't have to lie like that for her sake.
Was I being a showoff?
You don't have to shoulder the burden by yourself.
I still have other things on my mind, but...
Get on.
You have to find Lemerio, don't you?
Aren't you coming with me?
Matters of business don't concern me.
Are you still upset?
You're going to fall off if you don't hush.
F-Five hundred?
Yes.
Should we succeed in smuggling the gold in,
we'd like you to buy it for five hundred Lumione.
A-Absolutely not. Do you really think we have the funds to do that?
I'm not asking you to pay in full right now.
Sign a contract that will accommodate a gradual repayment of your debt within a period of ten years.
Five hundred is still out of the question.
You're the one who created a trading company that had the most impressive dock in town.
Five hundred Lumione in ten years must be child's play to you.
W-What are you doing?
I heard everything from Liebert-san.
Instead of running away with a paltry amount of money,
I'm sure it's in your best interests to concede to our demands and attempt to revive your company.
The bearer of the deed will be the Lohen Trading Union.
The union?
You might be able to betray a private trader like myself,
but you won't be able to get away with doing the same thing to a trading union.
I thought I'd never see you again!
This is for making me worry!
O-Ouch.
You son of a gun!
That's what you call filial devotion.
So now you just sell this ten year contract to me and never have to deal with Lemerio again.
How'd you do it?
It was a simple gold transaction,
but I can't tell you about the details.
Well, I'll buy it for thirty.
I'll pay an extra hundred if your deal goes through.
A hundred?
I'm in a cheerful mood. Think of it as a present.
Thank you very much.
That should be enough for me to cover all the apologies
and such I'll need to be making as well as my debt.
You really have become a full-fledged merchant.
Let's drink until we pass out as soon as I'm finished with work.
Well, I'm not sure I...
My companion...
You're late.
Sorry. What is it that you wanted to ask?
I have two questions.
Two?
First, how much trust do you have in that girl?
We can catch up to Norah if she tries to run away with the gold.
I didn't hand her the gold out of blind faith.
Well, I suppose that's that.
Your next question?
I'll answer anything you ask.
I owe you at least that much.
I...
want to get some fresh air.
Do you remember?
Whose name did you call when I confronted the girl and the dog?
I couldn't hear anything because I was caught up in the moment,
but I'm sure you called out someone's name.
Has it been eating at you?
No...
It's not that important.
I called out to you.
You just lied, didn't you?
Yes I did.
The truth is that I don't remember.
But...
But?
I must have called out to you if I take the circumstances into consideration.
It was a critical situation.
There's no doubt I would have instinctively chosen to call your name.
After all...
W-Wait!
All right. Go ahead.
After all...
Your name isn't as long as hers.
And if I'd said "Norah," it still would have been distinct even if I said it quickly.
On the other hand, I could have said Holo in less than a second.
It's entirely plausible that you could miss it if you were distracted.
What do you think? Pretty convincing, isn't it?
Shut up!
You called out my name because it isn't as long?
You fool!
What upsets me even more is the fact that you sincerely believe that!
I could have scratched you up to my heart's content if you had said you called out to that girl!
Fine.
I'll give you another chance.
Call out my name.
Holo.
It really is easy to say.
You fool!
Oh, that's right.
I owe you an explanation.
He was never in love with me.
He had just realized what I was.
I see.
He's a wonderful partner.
Much more useful than this man over here.
Don't get carried away.
I hope you two find happiness.
I found myself lost and alone on this journey
Though my heart wandered far and wide, I could move not an inch
But now I can depart for any distant land
Now that we've met on this road
Even the unfamiliar songs of travelers
Can spark nostalgia in me when I'm with you
If I could take your outstretched hand
Then how far could we go?
Let's set off to wherever we please
And bask in the sounds and smells of unfamiliar lands